this is the time known as the great pirate era a countless array of pirates go to battle across
the seas in search of the one piece the legendary treasure left behind by gold roger king of the
pirates monkey d luffy a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit set sail to
become the next king of the pirates as luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles they capture
the unwanted attention of the world government which will use any means necessary to stop them
can't wait to see what kind of adventures up next with a charted course awash in danger and intrigue
the crew will cut a path across the grand line to the new world
unable to save ace's life during the war of the best the injured luffy was taken to amazon living
where he fell into despair but this is a story from 10 years ago in the east blue when ace luffy and
their friend sabo made a promise to each other that they would become pirates sabo whose parents are
members of the nobility was kidnapped by his father and forced back to high town while his friends in
great terminal could only watch i'll do whatever you want me to okay i'll live whatever life you've
mapped out just please i'm begging you don't hurt my friends they've done nothing wrong i can't stand
this those two are my brothers it's important we all keep our mouths shut think what would happen if
someone outside of high town found out about the plan you and i are special we come from great noble
families
the fire has been set the great terminal in crisis
hold on wait a minute kid of course i know about the fire why what's wrong did they cancel it
blue jam and his men have been placing explosives all over great terminal just like we asked
oh my are you all right out of my way
i have to tell them
boy where are your parents learn some manners there's no time
settle down kid yeah just relax please loopy
huh we're burning down great terminal but why the hell would you want to do that
not so loud we gotta keep quiet about this if anyone finds out it won't work
you really are a meanie i knew we shouldn't have trusted you we gotta hurry and tell everyone
we can i told you to keep quiet hey shut them up i'm just following orders same as you
in case you didn't guess all those boxes you've been lugging around are filled with explosives
you get it nothing will survive that fire and no one
but blue jam don't do it since when did you brass start giving a damn about other people
well now that you know about the grand plan you're stuck here we can't risk letting you go
sorry actually there's something i've been meaning to ask you boys
so tell me is it true that you brats are hiding treasure somewhere around here
you've crossed me for the last time
sabo you've caused us nothing but disgrace from now on i'm through with your antics
it was right to adopt another child
open up dad please i gotta go warn them everyone in great terminal is going to die
please dad let me out this is serious
it's no use
Stupid dog!
Huh? Hey, wait. What's that?
Something weird is happening in Grey Terminal.
Helicon fire.
Who knew the plan would turn out to be this fun?
Hey, boss! Come quick! You gotta see this!
All right, what's the big deal?
Mr. Skye, look!
Is that the town?
No, it's closer than that.
I think it's Grey Terminal. It's on fire!
What's going on? Where's that smoke coming from?
Grey Terminal has never caught fire before.
What happened?
Edge Town is too dangerous! Evacuate immediately!
All residents, please head downtown!
Stay here where it's safe. We'll take care of the fire and other citizens.
The Great Gate!
We finally made it!
Hey! What are you doing?
We only protect the residents inside.
You're kidding!
Why are you doing this?
This is insane! Let us in, dammit!
Help us! We're begging you!
Everybody get up!
We gotta escape!
The fire almost has us surrounded!
Where did this mess even come from?
Look, it's no use, man.
Leave it behind and make a run for it.
Crap! The fire's already gotten to the shore!
The entrance to the forest is burning too!
We're all gonna die! Where do we go?!
We're all gonna die!
Say so long to this dump, fellas!
Good riddance!
It'll be easy living from here on out!
Yeah, just like the nobles. Heh.
Course not.
We couldn't care less about the living garbage stinking up Great Terminal.
But it makes a good hideout.
The place is huge, plus no law around to bug us, get it?
I'm aware of that.
But think, if you do this for me, well, you won't need a hideout.
I have the authority to make you and your crew bonafide nobles.
Really? You do that for us?
Once this is through, the King of Goa will give us titles!
We'll live in high-townest nobles!
No more of this trash heap!
Now, let's move.
We're almost done.
And don't worry.
Onto the Great Gate!
The military is waiting for us!
Captain, we left those two brats in the hideout.
Forget them.
They had their chance to join up when I asked them where their treasure was.
But they blew it.
Fools like them are gonna live long anyway.
Captain!
The gate is already closed!
It's nothing.
They just don't want other people to break in and cause a riot.
I'm supposed to give them a sign once we're here.
Then they'll open it up.
It's me, Blue Jam.
We're here.
Huh?
Hey!
Open the damn gate!
Captain.
You don't think.
Hey!
Come on!
What the hell are you doing?!
This isn't funny!
Open the gate!
We made a deal!
You're supposed to let us evacuate from this pit!
Quit screwing around and let us in!
You bunch of bastards!
The king made me a promise!
If we burn down a terminal he'd make us nobles!
Don't tell me he...
The king set us up!
That liar!
Damn it!
Did you hear?
They found out who started the fire!
It was some pirate named Blue Jam from Grey Terminal!
How despicable!
A criminal turning on his own men!
I bet he was trying to keep the world government's observers away so he could
keep on terrorizing people!
Gosh!
What an evil pirate!
It's way too hot, Ace!
I think I'm gonna melt!
Oh, you are!
Damn!
Why did Blue Jam rope us into this mess?
We can't get away!
I don't want to die!
If you don't stop complaining, I'll kill you!
I'm not that hard!
Oh, I'm burning!
I mean, this isn't so bad!
It's all over the place!
I can barely breathe!
I mean, I'm cool!
The fire will kill us all!
And we're gonna be fine!
Don't worry!
We'll live!
Somehow!
Someone called the police!
Sabo did it again!
Hello?
Police?
Anyone?
Hello?
Hey, are you nuts?
You're going the wrong way!
Open the gate now!
What are you talking about?
Don't breath!
Go home!
Luffy!
Ace!
Run!
Let go, brat!
Stay away from the lock!
Open the gate!
Stop!
No!
Why don't you be a good kid and get out of here!
Don't give us any more trouble!
I'm sorry!
Guys!
Ugh!
Don't give us any more trouble!
What happened to you, boy?
Who's there?
Whoever you are!
Listen!
The nobles are the ones behind this fire!
You gotta believe me!
Hightown wreaks worse than Great Terminal ever did!
The people act civilized, but on the inside they're all rotten!
They only care about making themselves look good no matter what it takes!
I can't stay here!
If I do, then I'll never be free!
I'm ashamed of being born noble!
I hate myself!
Goa Kingdom!
Look what you've done to this child!
How you've turned him against you!
I know how you feel!
I was born in this country too!
But I alone do not have the power to change this world!
And maybe I never will!
But at least, at least you're actually listening to me, aren't you?
Of course I am!
And I'll never forget!
Keep running, Luffy!
Don't stop!
It can't be!
Do something!
It's all over, isn't it?
It's too late to put out the fire, Captain!
We gotta abandon the ship!
The sea is blocked off anyway!
Damn it, King!
That filthy cheat thinks he can get away with this?
Just you wait!
You're dead!
Must Grey Terminal be an assault to my senses even in its final moments?
That light is far too bright!
We are sorry, Your Majesty.
Please, allow us to close the curtains.
Say, Papa, how come we want to burn everybody in Grey Terminal?
Aren't they people too, just like us?
Not exactly.
They chose to live meaningless lives.
Just think about it.
If they had chosen the path of high-class nobility like you and me, they wouldn't be in this mess.
They wouldn't?
I get it!
You mean it's their fault for being born all poor and dumb!
How silly!
Yes, now enough about those people.
You need to get some studying done before bedtime.
M'kay!
See you tomorrow.
It's blocked off here too.
Damn it!
We just keep losing ground!
I don't want to die like this!
Do you think all those old guys got away safe?
Who cares about them?
We're in trouble!
Crap!
I can't tell.
Where are we?
Who said you two brats were allowed to escape?
Blue jam!
How come you're still here?
I thought you were escaping after the fire got lit.
Did something happen?
Shut up, you punk!
It's hopeless.
You do know that, right?
There's a sort of irony to this.
It's a new perspective.
Humans are strange creatures.
I hit rock bottom, and all I can do is laugh about it.
They're acting really weird.
It's creepy.
Luffy, run for it!
Grab him!
Where do you think you're going?
We did this job together.
That means we get to die together.
We're not gonna die with you losers.
We don't give up that easy.
Is that so?
Actually, you still haven't told me where you're hiding that treasure.
Friends don't keep secrets from each other.
I'll save it for you before the fire reaches it.
All you have to do is tell me where it is.
Your life is in danger, and all you care about is treasure?
Well, if you don't want it, then you might as well tell me, right?
Damn it.
You've gone nuts.
I'm just trying to stop another tragedy.
I already saw my ship reduced to charcoal.
It'd be a shame if that happened to your treasure too.
All your hard work and for nothing.
You suck!
Get your own treasure!
All right, you win.
No!
You spent forever collecting that!
What would Sabo think?
Shut up!
Sabo would understand.
The treasure isn't important anymore.
The only thing that matters is getting out of here alive.
Six years.
We've collected treasure for six years and hit it in this tree.
Why, thank you.
Don't cry.
It's okay, Luffy.
This won't be the end.
What are you doing?
I told you where it is, now let us go!
I'm sorry.
I don't think I trust you.
Now then, about that treasure.
Let's go.
You can lead.
You moron.
That won't leave us time to escape.
And I'm not dying here.
Just go.
You've got the damn map.
Listen, kid.
Don't you dare piss me off.
I'm not above stealing from children or murdering them.
I'll have my revenge.
And believe me, those nobles will regret the day they crossed Blue Jam.
And to think you called one of them your brother.
They act like a little money and influence makes them a gift to the rest of the world.
Like it gives them the right to look down on us like we're trash.
Shut up!
Sabo isn't like that!
Take it back!
Yes, he is.
Face it.
Sure, you stayed together.
But he was looking down on you the whole time.
Liar!
His parents are loaded.
He doesn't have any of the problems that you or I deal with.
He used you idiots to get some kicks.
He was just bored.
Then got a taste of real life.
And he ran back home to his rich daddy.
That's enough.
Sabo is our brother.
He's right!
Sabo just wants to be free!
Lucy!
Say goodbye, kid.
Just let me go!
Get the hell away from Luffy!
You screwed up big time, brat!
Go on!
Try that crap again before I kill you!
Get off of me, you scumbag!
Time's up.
Ace, no!
Don't do it!
Even as the fires in Gray Terminal threaten to consume them, Ace and Luffy fight Blue Gem with all their might.
In the wake of the tragedy, Sabo decides to seize freedom in his hands and takes to the sea,
as a celestial dragon arrives in Hightown.
On the next, One Piece, where can freedom be found?
A sad departure of a boy!
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!
All news for today...
47 years of olarak, I'm going to be king of here in Manhattan.
In fact, like half a boy!
Come on up.
Win too!
The next new has been..
asına-seamos brevely!
All news forター!
Be very much time!
Swat on the whole house!
It's crazy!
Let go!
2 sano!
5eso game of the ???